Guide to the Witness to Guantanamo Video Collection, 2009-2017 RL.11691
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Interviews, 2009-2017; 10,000 Gigabytes secure server
  - Buehn, Bob, 2011-10-22; 2:06:38
    - Buehn, Bob - short clip - Did Not Know What Was Coming (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file Bob Buehn-Did Not Know What Was Coming.mp4)
    - Buehn, Bob - short clip - Right Intentions, Wrong Effects (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file Bob Buehn-Right Intentions, Wrong Effects.mp4)
    - Buehn, Bob - short clip - The Mayor of Guantanamo (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file Bob Buehn-The Mayor of Guantanamo.mp4)
  - Chekkouri, Redouane, 2012-07-11; 1:32:53
    Redouane Chekkouri, male, age 40, Moroccan, was detained in Guantanamo from April 30, 2002 until July 31, 2004, when he was returned to Morrocco. Upon returning to Morocco, Chekkouri (along with four other ex-Guantanamo detainees) was put on trial for charges related to terrorism, but was eventually acquitted in 2007.
    - Chekkouri, Redouane - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file RedouaneChekkouri.mov)
  - Chemerinsky, Erwin, 2010-03-10; 1:02:12
    Erwin Chemerinsky, male, age 56, is the founding Dean of the University of California, Irvine School of Law, and a top expert in constitutional law. He is the author of seven books and over 200 law review articles.
    - Chemerinsky, Erwin - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file ErwinChemerinsky.mov)
    - Chemerinsky, Erwin - short clip - Human (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file ErwinChemerinsky_Human.mp4)
    - Chemerinsky, Erwin - short clip - RuleofLaw (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file ErwinChemerinsky_RuleofLaw.mp4)
  - Clemente, Jim, 2010-06-13; 1:43:34
    Jim Clemente, male, age 50 was an FBI Supervisory Special Agent and was stationed in Guantanamo to consult on interrogation methods and the development of an interrogation plan. He took a public stand against the tactics being used, saying they violated the U.S. Torture Statute.
    - Clemente, Jim - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file JimClemente.mov)
    - Clemente, Jim - short clip - InterrogationMethods (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JimClemente_InterrogationMethods.mp4)
    - Clemente, Jim - short clip - InterrogationPlan (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JimClemente_InterrogationPlan.mp4)
  - Corn, Geoffrey, 2012-05-16; 1:05:22
    Geoffrey Corn, male, age 50, served in the United States military for 22 years, and was an expert witness for the Military Commissions in Guantanamo Bay.
    - Corn, Geoffrey - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file GeoffreyCorn.mov)
    - Corn, Geoffrey - short clip - JuryTrialsWouldn'tWork (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file GeoffreyCorn_JuryTrialsWouldn'tWork.mp4)
    - Corn, Geoffrey - short clip - JuryTrialsWouldn'tWork (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file GeoffreyCorn_JuryTrialsWouldn'tWork .mp4)
    - Corn, Geoffrey - short clip - Peacetimevs.Wartime (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file GeoffreyCornPeacetimevs.Wartime.mp4)
    - Corn, Geoffrey - short clip - WartimeDetentionIsInherentlyIndefinite (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file GeoffreyCorn_WartimeDetentionIsInherentlyIndefinite.mp4)
  - Corsetti, Damien, interview 1, 2013-03-04; 1:41:52
    Damien Corsetti, male, age 33, was an Army interrogator in Bagram, Afghanistan and Abu Ghraib, Iraq where he allegedly assaulted and mistreated prisoners, and was known as the "King of Torture." He was cleared by a military jury of all charges on June 1, 2006, and was honorably discharged from the United States Army.
    - Corsetti, Damien, interview 1 - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file DamienCorsetti.mov)
    - Corsetti, Damien, interview 1 - short clip - BendingLikeAPalmTreeInTheWind (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DamienCorsetti_BendingLikeAPalmTreeInTheWind.mp4)
  - Corsetti, Damien, interview 2, 2013-04-16; 2:24:46
    - Corsetti, Damien, interview 2 - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file DamienCorsetti2.mov)
    - Corsetti, Damien, interview 2 - short clip - DrunkonPowerat22 (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DamienCorsetti_DrunkonPowerat22.mp4)
  - Corsetti, Damien, interview 3, 2015-07-27; 1:09:32
    Damien Corsetti, male, age 35, was an Army interrogator in Bagram, Afghanistan and Abu Ghraib, Iraq where he allegedly assaulted and mistreated prisoners, and was known as the "King of Torture." He was cleared by a military jury of all charges on June 1, 2006, and was honorably discharged from the United States Army.
    - Corsetti, Damien, interview 3 - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file DamienCorsetti3shadowed.mov)
    - Corsetti, Damien, interview 3 - short clip - IllBeYourBadGuy (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DamienCorsetti_IllBeYourBadGuy.mp4)
  - Craig, Greg, 2011-11-04; 1:46:27
    He wants to approve transcript before release.
    Greg Craig, male, age 66, was White House Counsel from 2009 to 2010, and drafted the executive orders banning the use of torture by government personnel, and calling for the closure of the Guantanamo Bay Detention Center.
    - Craig, Greg - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file GregCraig.mov)
  - Crider, Cori, 2015-07-16; 0:31:50
    Cori Crider, female, age 33, is an attorney and former Legal Director of Reprieve, and has represented many Guantanamo Bay detainees.
    - Crider, Cori - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file CoriCrider.mov)
    - Crider, Cori - short clip - AllThisTime (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file CoriCrider_AllThisTime.mp4)
    - Crider, Cori - short clip - CanLawyeringGetDetaineesOut (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file CoriCrider_CanLawyeringGetDetaineesOut.mp4)
    - Crider, Cori - short clip - ScarecrowsandBogeymen (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file CoriCrider_ScarecrowsandBogeymen.mp4)
  - Crosby, Sondra, 2016-07-03; 1:00:41
    Sondra Crosby, female, age 56, is co-founder and co-director of the Boston University Forensic Medical Evaluation Group, which provides medical forensic documentation of torture and other physical abuse. She was one of the first civilian doctors permitted to independently examine detainees while still in Guantanamo.
    - Crosby, Sondra - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file SondraCrosby.mov)
    - Crosby, Sondra - short clip - RetraumatizingDetainees (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file SondraCrosby_RetraumatizingDetainees.mp4)
    - Crosby, Sondra - short clip - SaudiArabianTerroristRehabilitationProgram (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file SondraCrosby_SaudiArabianTerroristRehabilitationProgram.mp4)
  - Dakwar, Jamil, 2016-05-24; 2:14:45
    Jamil Dakwar, male, age 42, is Director of the American Civil Liberties Union's Human Rights Program, which includes work on counter-terrorism and Guantanamo. He is also the ACLU's Main Representative to the United Nations, and has testified on the U.S.'s human rights violations in that capacity.
    - Dakwar, Jamil - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file JamilDakwar.mov)
    - Dakwar, Jamil - short clip - HoldingtheUSAccountable (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JamilDakwar_HoldingtheUSAccountable.mp4)
    - Dakwar, Jamil - short clip - HumanRightsViolationsAreNowFairGame (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JamilDakwar_HumanRightsViolationsAreNowFairGame.mp4)
    - Dakwar, Jamil - short clip - HumanRightsViolationsAreNowFairGame (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JamilDakwar_HumanRightsViolationsAreNowFairGame.mp4)
  - Davis, Morris, 2010-06-13; 2:05:34
    Morris Davis, male, age 51, was appointed as the third Chief Prosecutor in the Guantanamo military commissions in September 2005. He resigned from the position in October 2007.
    - Davis, Morris - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file MorrisDavis.mov)
    - Davis, Morris - short clip - BigBrains (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MorrisDavis_BigBrains.mp4)
    - Davis, Morris - short clip - LosetoWin (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MorrisDavis_LosetoWin.mp4)
    - Davis, Morris - short clip - Suicides (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MorrisDavis_Suicides.mp4)
  - Denbeaux, Mark, 2010-10-13; 1:29:45
    Mark Denbeaux, male, age 67, is a law professor and the director of the Center for Policy and Research at Seton Hall University School of Law. The Center has directed numerous studies on the Guantanamo Bay detention camp and its operations, based on data by the United States Department of Defense, and testified on the findings to Congress.
    - Denbeaux, Mark - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file MarkDenbeaux.mov)
    - Denbeaux, Mark - short clip - ChangingtheDebateonGuantanamo (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MarkDenbeaux_ChangingtheDebateonGuantanamo.mp4)
    - Denbeaux, Mark - short clip - EveryDetaineeLost (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MarkDenbeaux_EveryDetaineeLost.mp4)
  - Dergoul, Tarek, 2009-08-20; 2:21:42
    Tarek Dergoul, male, age 32, a British citizen of Moroccan descent, was detained in Guantanamo from May 2, 2002 until March 9, 2004, when he was returned to Britain.
    - Dergoul, Tarek - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file TarekDergoul.mov)
  - Diaz, Matt, 2011-11-05; 1:32:55
    Matt Diaz, male, age 46, was deputy director of the Guantanamo detention center's legal office from July 2004 until January 2005. Because of concerns about the legal and physical treatment of the detainees, he sent an anonymous card to the Center for Constitutional Rights revealing the 550 previously unreleased names of the detainees. He was later convicted of criminal charges and given a six-month sentence.
    - Diaz, Matt - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file MattDiaz.mov)
    - Diaz, Matt - short clip - LegalProcessinGuantanamo (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MattDiaz_LegalProcessinGuantanamo.mp4)
    - Diaz, Matt - short clip - ReleasingtheNames (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MattDiaz_ReleasingtheNames.mp4)
    - Diaz, Matt - short clip - SofterLanding (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MattDiaz_SofterLanding.mp4)
  - Dixon, J. Wells, 2014-05-13; 2:08:25
    J. Wells Dixon, male, age 42, is Senior Staff Attorney at the Center for Constitutional Rights, where he specializes in challenging unlawful Guantanamo detentions in federal court, before the military commissions at Guantanamo, and in international proceedings.
    - Dixon, J. Wells - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file JWellsDixon.mov)
    - Dixon, J. Wells - short clip - FailuretoClose (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JWellsDixon_FailuretoClose.mp4)
    - Dixon, J. Wells - short clip - GuantanamoandtheAmericanLandscape (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JWellsDixon_GuantanamoandtheAmericanLandscape.mp4)
  - Edney, Dennis, 2012-03-09; 1:58:32
    Dennis Edney, male, age 65, has been representing Canadian citizen Omar Khadr--who was captured and brought to Guantanamo as a juvenile--for over a decade.
    - Edney, Dennis - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file DennisEdney.mov)
    - Edney, Dennis - short clip - BrokenBird (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DennisEdney_BrokenBird.mp4)
    - Edney, Dennis - short clip - CanadianSupremeCourtsBraveDecision (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DennisEdney_CanadianSupremeCourtsBraveDecision.mp4)
    - Edney, Dennis - short clip - ConnectingWithOmar (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DennisEdney_ConnectingWithOmar.mp4)
  - Fallon, Mark, 2013-10-25; 2:00:52
    Mark Fallon, male, age 56, served for more than 30 years in the federal law enforcement and counterintelligence community, including as Naval Criminal Investigative Service (NCIS) Special Agent, and Assistant Director for Training at the Federal Law Enforcement Training Center within the Department of Homeland Security.
    - Fallon, Mark - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file MarkFallon.mov)
    - Fallon, Mark - short clip - AnOpportunityLost (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MarkFallon_AnOpportunityLost.mp4)
    - Fallon, Mark - short clip - AnOpportunityLost-newwm (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MarkFallon-AnOpportunityLost-newwm.mp4)
    - Fallon, Mark - short clip - ConflictingInterrogationTechniques (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MarkFallon_ConflictingInterrogationTechniques.mp4)
    - Fallon, Mark - short clip - ConflictingInterrogationTechniques-newwm (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MarkFallon_ConflictingInterrogationTechniques-newwm.mp4)
    - Fallon, Mark - short clip - Treatmentofthe20thHijacker (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MarkFallon_Treatmentofthe20thHijacker.mp4)
    - Fallon, Mark - short clip - Treatmentofthe20thHijacker-newwm (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MarkFallon_Treatmentofthe20thHijacker-newwm.mp4)
  - Frakt, David, 2010-05-17; 1:42:30
    David Frakt, male, age 40, was an attorney with the US Air Force Reserve JAG Corps and represented Guantanamo detainees facing trial by military tribunal.
    - Frakt, David - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file DavidFrakt.mov)
    - Frakt, David - short clip - FrequentFlier (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DavidFrakt_FrequentFlier.mp4)
    - Frakt, David - short clip - JawadsConfession (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DavidFrakt_JawadsConfession.mp4)
    - Frakt, David - short clip - JawadsConfession (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DavidFrakt_JawadsConfession.mp4)
    - Frakt, David - short clip - TwoPeeRule (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DavidFrakt_TwoPeeRule.mp4)
  - Gelles, Michael, 2011-03-11; 1:14:32
    Michael Gelles, male, age 51, is the former Chief Psychologist for the Navy Criminal Investigative Service (NCIS) at Guantanamo. He notably uncovered the unauthorized use of abusive interrogation techniques of detainees.
    - Gelles, Michael - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file MichaelGelles.mov)
    - Gelles, Michael - short clip - CoerciveTechniquesProduceUnreliableInformation (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MichaelGelles_CoerciveTechniquesProduceUnreliableInformation.mp4)
    - Gelles, Michael - short clip - IsolationAsARelationshipBuildingTool (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MichaelGelles_IsolationAsARelationshipBuildingTool.mp4)
    - Gelles, Michael - short clip - RiskAssessmentDuringDetaineeReleaseProcess (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MichaelGelles_RiskAssessmentDuringDetaineeReleaseProcess.mp4)
  - Gorman, Candace, 2011-02-01; 1:53:07
    Candace Gorman, female, age 56, shut down her civil rights practice to focus solely on getting her two clients out of Guantanamo, closing Guantanamo and bringing those responsible for these war crimes to justice.
    - Gorman, Candace - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file CandaceGorman.mov)
    - Gorman, Candace - short clip - Al-GhizzawiPreparesForDeath (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file CandaceGorman_Al-GhizzawiPreparesForDeath.mp4)
    - Gorman, Candace - short clip - BadReflectionOnOurCourts (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file CandaceGorman_BadReflectionOnOurCourts.mp4)
    - Gorman, Candace - short clip - TurnOverTheArab (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file CandaceGorman_TurnOverTheArab.mp4)
  - Guter, Donald, 2012-05-16; 1:30:22
    Donald Guter, male, age 63, was a JAG Admiral and served as special counsel to the Chief of Naval Operations. He became the 37th Judge Advocate General of the Navy from 2000-2002.
    - Guter, Donald - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file DonaldGuter.mov)
    - Guter, Donald - short clip - ConfrontingJimHaynesAbouttheLackofInformation (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DonaldGuter_ConfrontingJimHaynesAbouttheLackofInformation.mp4)
    - Guter, Donald - short clip - ConfrontingJimHaynesAbouttheLackofInformation-review (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DonaldGuter_ConfrontingJimHaynesAbouttheLackofInformation-review.mp4)
    - Guter, Donald - short clip - WhoseIdeaWasGuantanamo (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DonaldGuter_WhoseIdeaWasGuantanamo.mp4)
    - Guter, Donald - short clip - WhoseIdeaWasGuantanamo-review (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DonaldGuter_WhoseIdeaWasGuantanamo-review.mp4)
    - Guter, Donald - short clip - WillingtoTradeValuesforSafety (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DonaldGuter_WillingtoTradeValuesforSafety.mp4)
    - Guter, Donald - short clip - WillingtoTradeValuesforSafety-review (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file DonaldGuter_WillingtoTradeValuesforSafety-review.mp4)
  - Gutierrez, Gitanjali, 2011-10-21; 2:33:40
    Gitanjali Gutierrez, female, age 41, is an attorney with the Center for Constitutional Rights, and was the first habeas lawyer to visit her clients in Guantanamo in September 2004.
    - Gutierrez, Gitanjali - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file GitanjaliGutierrez.mov)
    - Gutierrez, Gitanjali - short clip - DemandingAccessToHerClient (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file GitanjaliGutierrez_DemandingAccessToHerClient.mp4)
    - Gutierrez, Gitanjali - short clip - SuicidalClient (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file GitanjaliGutierrez_SuicidalClient.mp4)
    - Gutierrez, Gitanjali - short clip - UsedtoConcealTorture (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file GitanjaliGutierrez_UsedtoConcealTorture.mp4)
  - Habib, Maha, 2012-01-05; 1:01:31
    Maha Habib, female, age 47, is the wife of Mamdouh Habib, an Australian citizen detained in Guantanamo from May 5, 2002 until January 27, 2005, and was then returned to Australia.
    - Habib, Maha - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file MahaHabib.mov)
    - Habib, Maha - short clip - ATestFromGod (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MahaHabib_ATestFromGod.mp4)
    - Habib, Maha - short clip - HearingtheNews (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file MahaHabib_HearingtheNews.mp4)
  - Habib,Mamdouh, 2011-12-30; 1:44:19
    Mamdouh Habib, male, age 56, Egyptian-born Australian citizen, was detained in Guantanamo from May 5, 2002 until January 27, 2005, when he was returned to Australia.
    - Habib,Mamdouh - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file MamdouhHabib.mov)
  - Hafetz, Jonathan, 2010-04-16; 1:43:21
    Jonathan Hafetz, male, age unknown, works for the National Security Project of the American Civil Liberties Union, has helped coordinate the Guantanamo detainee habeas corpus litigation since its earliest stages, including testifying before Congress.
    - Hafetz, Jonathan - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file JonathanHafetz.mov)
    - Hafetz, Jonathan - short clip - JewishLawyers (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JonathanHafetz_JewishLawyers.mp4)
    - Hafetz, Jonathan - short clip - SoftTorture (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JonathanHafetz_SoftTorture.mp4)
  - Hajj, Sami Al, 2012-07-13; 2:11:04
    Sami Al Hajj, male, age 43, Sudanese, was detained in Guantanamo from June 14, 2002 until April 30, 2008, when he was released without charge to Sudan. While in Guantanamo, he went on a hunger strike to protest the conditions, and refused to end his strike until he was released.
    - Hajj, Sami Al - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file SamiAlHajj.mov)
    - Hajj, Sami Al - short clip - BeingReleased (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file SamiAlHajj_BeingReleased.mp4)
    - Hajj, Sami Al - short clip - TheGoodThatCameOutofIt (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file SamiAlHajj_TheGoodThatCameOutofIt.mp4)
  - Hakimjan, Adil, 2014-06-17; 2:37:47
    Adil Hakimjan, male, age 39, a Uyghur from the Xinjiang autonomous region, was detained in Guantanamo from June 2002 until May 5, 2006. In April 2009, he was granted asylum in Sweden.
    - Hakimjan, Adil - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file AdilHakimjan.mov)
  - Hakimjan,Kauvser, 2014-06-16; 0:41:51
    Kauvser Hakimjan, female, age 40, is the sister of former Guantanamo detainee Adil Hakimjan. They were reunited in Albania in 2006, and both granted asylum in Sweden in 2009.
    - Hakimjan,Kauvser - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file KauvserHakimjanShadowed.mov)
  - Hall, Julia, 2014-08-19; 1:26:15
    Julia Hall, female, age 51, is Amnesty International's expert on counter terrorism and human rights. Previously, as senior legal counsel in Terrorism and Counter-Terrorism at Human Rights Watch, she monitored the Guantanamo military commissions trial of Salim Hamdan.
    - Hall, Julia - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file JuliaHall.mov)
    - Hall, Julia - short clip - GlobalParadigmShift (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JuliaHall_GlobalParadigmShift.mp4)
    - Hall, Julia - short clip - GlobalParadigmShift (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JuliaHall_GlobalParadigmShift.mp4)
    - Hall, Julia - short clip - NobodyWantsThem (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JuliaHall_NobodyWantsThem.mp4)
    - Hall, Julia - short clip - TheWayGuantanamoWillClose (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JuliaHall_TheWayGuantanamoWillClose.mp4)
  - Hami, Rafiq Al, 2012-07-18; 1:54:38
    Rafiq Al Hami, male, age 43, Tunisian, was detained in Guantanamo seven years, five of which were spent in solitary confinement, from February 2003 until January 24, 2010, when he was transferred to Slovakia. In 2013, he left his Tunisian family and small business to join an armed group in Syria, and two years later his family were told he had been killed.
    - Hami, Rafiq Al - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file RafiqAlHami.mov)
  - Hamlin, Janet, 2017-10-01; 1:26:21
    Janet Hamlin, female, age 56, has been the only courtroom sketch artist for the Guantanamo Bay military commission hearings from 2006 to the present time. Because cameras are not permitted during hearings, Hamlin's work provides the only visual representation available.
    - Hamlin, Janet - Interview master file (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0001, Video-file JanetHamlin.mov)
    - Hamlin, Janet - short clip - ASurprisingArtDirector (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JanetHamlin_ASurprisingArtDirector.mp4)
    - Hamlin, Janet - short clip - SketchingGuantanamo (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JanetHamlin_SketchingGuantanamo.mp4)
    - Hamlin, Janet - short clip - TheLastTransparency (Digital-materials RL11691-SET-0003, Video-file JanetHamlin_TheLastTransparency.mp4)
  - Hénin, Nicolas, 2010-09-26; 1:45:20
    Nicolas Hénin, male, age 39, a French journalist, was held captive by ISIS militants from June 2013 until April 2014. As a freelance journalist, he covered the conflict in Iraq from 2002 to 2004, and subsequent crises and conflicts in Sudan, Somalia and Yemen.